It has happened
that today I would like to tell you how
ICICI Bank
trapped me in a fake manner at its ICICI Lombard.
I had cheated ICICI Bank and had taken a
housing loan of Rs. 6 lakh in 2006
in its embrace. Some papers were signed by me
after some time. Some women got angry and
found out that a black paper was written in the paper to subscribe.
ICICI Bank had subscribed me for 15-17 months from my account. They
told me that a sum of
Rs. 40 thousand was
given in my name to ICICI Insurance Company ICICI Lombard by
adding the premium of many years of insurance in my
name without my consent, about which
I was not told anything.
Now on contacting me many times, on writing letters, on
emailing, there was
no copy of proper complete documents.
Meena was not given the documents which were given to me. After
looking at them with great difficulty, after doing a lot of prayers, on
Saturday, it was not
available. After looking at them on Monday, it is clear that
they have set up my
ICICI Lombard form at many places. Click on
me.  I was told whether the building has been fire
insured or
not,
Papa, if it is not, then the premium is approximately Rs. 4000,
whereas in the name of loan, Rs. 517 is being
taken, approximately Rs. 500 per year,
and this also a loan was taken in my name,
which after my
loan was over, I have taken it on loan, it has been
many years since I started paying it, it could be
five-six years or even more, I am
not sure of the date, it would be in the file, in the records and papers, even
after that, they are
deducting Rs. 517 per month and going away, I am
not being given any proof, I
received the loan cheque that if the loan is in your name,
then its cheque is given to you, to the
devotees of the person whose payment has to be made,
and I have never applied for a loan for insurance, they are
not giving any proof of it, I have given the proof of the application
in the application, start a loan in my name,
Pirai Historians company
ICICI Lombard, whichever one you get,
such document is not available, if you get
insurance then you pay the annual premium every time  I had taken
some insurance, this cream is filled,
who keeps taking the premium collected for many years, what is the system about this,
I have been cheated for many years
and the loan has been closed, it must be many years
but due to the game played by both of them,
I am still being charged Rs. 517 for fair
insurance which amounts to about
Rs. 500 per year,
all my money should be returned along with 18 percent annual interest
and harassment legal action cases, the
administration should return it to the government,
whoever you want to take this case against them, you
know this government or administration
harasses you by running around your corners for years,
despite this no action is being taken against them
nor is anyone else taking any action,
when I contacted the bank and talked to
you, they said
that you people are
taking Rs. 100 per year, whereas you all know that
premium is charged every year on taking any insurance,
they have
collected premium of many years together and
showing loan in my name  By making a fake signature, he has
cheated me by depositing it with me and
gave it to his brother ICICI Lombard. At
that time, the bank
subscribed for reducing the interest, in
which the
appointed people were
told at many places that it has been
appointed for this,
when I told this, then
after a lot of flirting and forcing, I was told that by
insuring your plot for 56 lakhs, which is a
yearly interest, for that, after
collecting preventive measures for many years, we have given this
to ICICI Lombard without your consent. The
bank has not given 500 rupees subscription for dual app, to
give it to the insurance company, it was not
given to me after checking the name of ICICI Lombard, it was
appointed to give it to the insurance company, so by doing this,
anyone can
take 5 lakh crore rupees in my name and give
it to anyone, see this,
how these people are protesting this fraud of ICICI Bank,
both of them together are requesting my government with support in ICICI Bank,
ICICI Lombard,
we will complete this as soon as possible and get me insured on 18th,
St. John's and many other things.  There should be compensation, my money should be
returned, no one is listening, this
post keeps circling and bothering me
[Music]